ican-ngr.org 2011-11-25

# 

    THE INSTITUTE OF CHARTERED ACCOUNTANTS OF NIGERIA (ICAN) Privacy Policy 
    PLEASE READ THIS AGREEMENT CAREFULLY 
    
    ICAN respects and take steps to ensure your privacy is protected and our site safe for everyone who visits and use its services. Our committment is to provide you the best possible online service and experience. The purpose of this policy statement is to inform you:
    
    How we use the information 
    With whom we share the information
    
    How you can change the information
    
    This policy addresses our practices with respect to our website, but does not address the practices of any website we link to (including the merchants and content providers we link to). This policy is incorporated into, and subject to the terms of, our User Agreement. 
    
    How We Use Information collected
    We use information which you provide us to keep track of the ICAN services you have signed up to receive. We may also use personally identifiable information about you to improve our marketing and promotional efforts, to statistically analyse site usage, to improve our content and service offerings and to customise our site's content and layout. We do this in an attempt to improve our site and better tailor it to meet our users' needs. We may also use personally identifiable information about you to deliver information to you that, in some cases, is targeted to your interests. We use your email address to contact you regarding administrative notices or latest news about the Institute from time to time. We use information in the file we maintain about you, and other information we obtain from your current and past activities on the site, to resolve disputes, troubleshoot problems and enforce our Terms and Conditions. 
    
    Protection of Database Information
    Any information sent to ICAN for Service Payment and or storage purposes will remain the property of the account holder. ICAN will at no time collect or redistribute this information without your consent, except where legally required by law to do so. This is with particular reference to any database, numbers and/or recipient details that you may deliver to us, or store on our databases. 
    
    Disclosure of Your Information
    We do not sell or rent any personally identifiable information about you to any third party. We must comply with court orders, information requests from government agencies and regulators and other legal and regulatory processes that may require the disclosure of your personally-identifiable information. 

    Reviewing/Changing Your Information
    If at any time you would like to change any information in your account, Login to the relevant page. Here you can change or update your information. 
    
    Limits on Our Abilities
    Although your privacy is very important to us, due to the existing legal and technical environment, we cannot ensure that your personally identifiable information will not be disclosed to third parties in ways not described in this policy. Additionally, we can (and you authorize us to) disclose any information about you to private entities, law enforcement or other government officials as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate to address or resolve inquiries or problems. This will not be done for commercial purposes or gain from ICAN as such.
    
    If you have further questions about our privacy policy or its implementation, please contact us.
    
    You acknowledge that acceptance of this privacy policy is a condition to your use of our services and you agree to be bound by all of its terms and conditions
